<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud, DevOps, Databases &amp; AI with Michael</title>
    <link>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cloud, DevOps, Databases &amp; AI with Michael</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI Updates</title>
      <link>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/2024/june/ai-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/2024/june/ai-updates/</guid>
      <description>AI main updates 19th June 2024&#xA;Claude 3.5 Sonnet was released. If you compare it with other LLM models, it does fairly well:&#xA;(Reference: https://www.anthropic.com/news/claude-3-5-sonnet)&#xA;13th May 2024&#xA;Check out new GPT-4o model, lot cheaper and better compared to some of previous GPT models&#xA;Written By Michael Agarwal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Updates</title>
      <link>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/2024/june/azure-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/2024/june/azure-updates/</guid>
      <description>Azure main updates for month of May Azure Virtual Network Manager’s virtual network verifier feature is now in public preview, enabling you to check if your network policies allow or disallow traffic between your Azure network resources.&#xA;Azure Load Balancer now supports health event logs to help you identify and troubleshoot ongoing issues affecting your load balancer resource’s health.&#xA;VM hibernation for general-purpose VMs is now generally available in all public regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Updates</title>
      <link>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/2020/jan/aws-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/2020/jan/aws-updates/</guid>
      <description>AWS main updates week of 06/17/2024 FOCUS is a new open-source cloud billing data specification that provides standardization to simplify cloud financial management across multiple sources. Data Exports for FOCUS 1.0 includes several AWS-specific columns, such as usage types and cost categories, and delivers exports on a daily basis to Amazon S3 as Parquet or CSV files.&#xA;Anthropic’s Claude 3.5 Sonnet foundation model is now generally available in Amazon Bedrock. That was fast :-)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content Via Hugo</title>
      <link>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/2020/jan/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://michaelagarwal.github.io/content/post/2020/jan/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>Hugo ships with several Built-in Shortcodes for rich content, along with a Privacy Config and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&#xA;YouTube privacy enhanced shortcode The youtube shortcode embeds a responsive video player for YouTube videos. Only the ID of the video is required, e.g.:&#xA;YouTube URL:&#xA;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3qHkcs3kG44 Shortcode:&#xA;{{&amp;lt; youtube 3qHkcs3kG44 &amp;gt;}} Rendered output: Headings&#xA;To create a heading, add number signs (#) in front of a word or phrase.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
